-And is served by staff on the outside and the inside who ensure that the staff in the chamber system has a good environment.
Here we are inside the chamber center wall to wall with the chamber hall.
From here we take care of pressure increase and pressure reduction and other monitoring of the chamber system.
The business is led by chamberwear leaders who have a number of chamber operators to their help-
-On the outside and chamber caretaker on the inside.
After about the Chamber Center is Belos Gym, decorated on two floors.
Here on the upper are workout bikes and treadmills for fitness training-
-And downstairs is the actual gym with equipment for strength and agility training.
Here we see a seaman's cabin located at the bottom of the ship on the tires where it actually swings least and is the quietest.
The sailors live in single cabins with a common toilet and shower department.
A tire up is also a sauna where you can warm up after a cold working day on deck or after a diving assignment
-What means that we have generators that produce power that then operate the ship's propellers.
Machine staff continuously control the various technical systems on board
-To ensure progress.
In the space next door is the control room from where the engine room's input system is monitored.
During a guard, machine and control rooms are staffed by an officer and a motor.
Here we are inside the fair where we can have a cup of coffee and unwind after the work session.
There is also the opportunity for crew collections and meetings as well as a little finer dinner sitting.
There is also a TV corner and a small library in the fair.
The fair also serves as a medical place where our doctor and our healthcare providers take care of any injury cases.
Here we see Belo's wet dive clock that is housed in a container on deck.
The clock is staffed by two divers who are raised with relatively heavy equipment down to the dive object.
Belo's dive system can use both air and mixed gas depending on dive depth and can be used down to 90 meters depth.
Welcome to the diving center.
From the dive center, all underwater activities that Belos can perform.
In here, the diving leader is for the wet clock diving.
The dive leader has control at times for downs and ascent and leads the divers' jobs on the dive object.
In the dive center also sits the supervisor for the operations with our underwater vessels or prey: er
The prey pilots here have their operator sites from which they control our various underwater vehicles.